https://www.churcharmy.com.au/privacy-policy/

Skip to Main Content
Privacy Policy
Church Army in Australia respects the privacy of its members, supporters, students and friends. We are bound by the National Privacy Principles set out in the Commonwealth of Australia Privacy Act 1988 (commonly referred to as The Privacy Act).
Personal Information
We routinely collect personal information such as a person’s name, age, contact details, and necessary financial information in order to provide receipts for donations, to maintain communication and to fulfil our obligations to students. We may at times collect other personal information as well. When we collect sensitive information (as defined in the Privacy Act) we will collect it with the consent of the person, unless the law allows us to collect it without their consent.
Where a person does not provide adequate personal information we may not be able to process donations, maintain communication or accept a student enrolment.
How we collect personal information
Church Army in Australia collections personal information in a number of ways, including:
Directly from persons completing documents such as a donation slip or application form
From third parties
From publicly available sources of information
From our own records
From the Church Army in Australia website (www.churcharmy.com.au) and the associated NAB secure server for receiving donations.
How we use personal information
Personal information may be used in order to:
Process donations
Communicate needs and news from Church Army in Australia, our members and our projects
Administer and manage our services, including charging and billing for services
Inform persons of ways the services provided to you could be improved
Conduct appropriate checks for credit-worthiness and for fraud
Research and develop our services
Gain an understanding of your information and communication needs in order for us to provide you with better service
